[
  {
    "question": "Who is Tony Starks father?",
    "answer": "Howard Stark"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does SHIELD stand for?",
    "answer": "Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Carol Danvers' nickname for Monica Rambeau?",
    "answer": "Lieutenant Trouble"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was responsible for King T'Chaka's death?",
    "answer": "Helmut Zemo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wanda and her brother Pietro are from where?",
    "answer": "Sokovia"
  },
  {
    "question": "On what planet was the Soul Stone in Infinity War?",
    "answer": "Vormir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nick Fury wears an eye patch over which eye?",
    "answer": "left"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Peggy tell Steve she wants to meet him for a dance?",
    "answer": "The Stork Club"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who founded SWORD?",
    "answer": "Maria Rambeau"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the names of Wanda's twins?",
    "answer": "Billy and Tommy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the motto/slogan of the Flag Smashers?",
    "answer": "One world, one people"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what town was Wanda's hex located?",
    "answer": "Westview, New Jersey"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does S.W.O.R.D. stand for in WandaVision",
    "answer": "Sentient Weapon Observation Response Division"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's Mordo's full name?",
    "answer": "Karl Mordo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Doctors Strange's cape?",
    "answer": "Cloak of Levitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years was Captain America trapped in the ice?",
    "answer": "66",
    "ignore": [
      "year",
      "years"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the call sign Maria Rambeau uses when flying with Carol Danvers in Captain Marvel?",
    "answer": "Photon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Black Panther's little sister?",
    "answer": "Shuri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thor's 4 friends from Asgard?",
    "answer": "Lady Sif; Hogun; Fandral; Volstagg"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Thano's home planet?",
    "answer": "Titan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does JARVIS stand for?",
    "answer": "Just a Rather Very Intelligent System"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does FRIDAY stand for?",
    "answer": "Female Replacement Intelligent Digital Assistant Youth"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does EDITH stand for?",
    "answer": "Even Dead I'm the Hero"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the dwarf who made Thanos’s gauntlet?",
    "answer": "Eitri"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the drone piloted by Sam Wilson in Captain America: Civil War?",
    "answer": "Redwing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the man who turned Steve Rogers into Captain America?",
    "answer": "Dr. Abraham Erskine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Yellowjacket from Ant-man?",
    "answer": "Darren Cross"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Odin’s trusted Asgardian horse in Thor?",
    "answer": "Sleipnir"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the artificial intelligence in Spider-Man’s suit?",
    "answer": "Karen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Loki's real father?",
    "answer": "Laufey"
  },
  {
    "question": "Main villian of Thor Dark World?",
    "answer": "Malekith"
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately, how old is Thor?",
    "answer": "1500"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many cameos did Stan Lee have?",
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "What group was Captain Marvel a member of?",
    "answer": "Starforce"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language is spoken in Wakanda?",
    "answer": "Xhosa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the prison the Guardians of the Galaxy escape from?",
    "answer": "The Kyln"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name of the group Thanos leads",
    "answer": "The Black Order"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Peter Parker's School?",
    "answer": "Midtown School of Science and Technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Killmongers real name?",
    "answer": "Erik Stevens"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Hawkeye's wife?",
    "answer": "Laura Barton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Peter Parker's best friend's name?",
    "answer": "Ned Leeds"
  },
  {
    "question": "What planet is Gamora from?",
    "answer": "Zen-Whoberi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the new captain America?",
    "answer": "John Walker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the leader of the Flag Smashers?",
    "answer": "Karli Morgenthau"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does B.A.R.F. stand for?",
    "answer": "Binarily Augmented Retro-Framing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created B.A.R.F.?",
    "answer": "Quentin Beck"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Whiplash?",
    "answer": "Ivan Vanko"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Mandarin?",
    "answer": "Xu Wenwu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Valkyrie's number?",
    "answer": "142",
    "ignore": [
      "Scrapper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the AI from Captain Marvel?",
    "answer": "Supreme Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the project from Captain Marvel?",
    "answer": "Pegasus",
    "ignore": [
      "Project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What species is Groot?",
    "answer": "Flora Colossus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped Tony Stark build Mark 1?",
    "answer": "Ho Yinsen"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Ghost from Ant Man and the WASP?",
    "answer": "Ava Starr"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who constantly uses magic to heal his arms?",
    "answer": "Jonathan Pangborn"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Red Skulls real name?",
    "answer": "Johann Schmidt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Thor's Grandfather?",
    "answer": "Bor"
  },
  {
    "question": "SHIELD headquarters is located in what building?",
    "answer": "Triskelion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for the all-female soldiers of Wakanda?",
    "answer": "Dora Milaje"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Kree homeworld?",
    "answer": "Hala"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name of the village from the end of Shang Chi 10 Rings?",
    "answer": "Ta Lo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the full name of the female Loki?",
    "answer": "Sylvie Laufeydottir"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Kate Bishop name the stray dog she found?",
    "answer": "Lucky the Pizza Dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Collector?",
    "answer": "Taneleer Tivan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What planet held the power stone?",
    "answer": "Morag"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who are Thor's 3 earth friends?",
    "answer": "Jane Foster; Erik Selvig; Darcy Lewis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Thanos retreat to after snapping?",
    "answer": "Planet 0259-S (the Garden)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Rocket's childhood friends?",
    "answer": "Lylla, Teefs, Floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "where to captain america and tony stark go back to in endgame?",
    "answer": "Camp Lehigh"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Grandmaster's name?",
    "answer": "En Dwi Gast"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who are Ant-man's closest friends?",
    "answer": "Luis, Kurt Goreshter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who leads the Dora Milaje?",
    "answer": "Okoye, then Ayo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the bad guy in Captain Marvel?",
    "answer": "Yon-Rogg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the good guy Skrull?",
    "answer": "Talos"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the names of Clint Barton's kids?",
    "answer": "Lila, Cooper, Nathaniel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who killed Frigga?",
    "answer": "Kurse"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the wifi password for Kamar Taj?",
    "answer": "Shamballa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who discovered the 10 rings?",
    "answer": "Xu Wenwu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Shang-chi's mother?",
    "answer": "Ying Li"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the ancient one?",
    "answer": "Yao"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the name of the missle that Tony has to recreate?",
    "answer": "Jericho"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the vultures real name?",
    "answer": "Adrian Toomes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Killmonger's Wakandan name?",
    "answer": "N'Jadaka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the bifrost sword?",
    "answer": "Hofund"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Valkyrie's real name?",
    "answer": "Brunnhilde"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Captain America's group in WWII?",
    "answer": "Howling Commandos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is posing as a SHIELD agent for hydra?",
    "answer": "Crossbones (Brock Rumlow)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the celestial inside earth during the Eternals?",
    "answer": "Tiamut the Communicator"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the names of Wanda and Vision's magic act names?",
    "answer": "Illusion and Glamour"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the youtube channel from Ms. Marvel?",
    "answer": "Sloth Baby Production"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the ship that Asgard escaped on at the end of Ragnorak?",
    "answer": "The Statesman"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Iron First, who is the leader of The Hand?",
    "answer": "Bakuto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the nightclub in Luke Cage?",
    "answer": "Harlem's Paradise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who trains Matt Murdock?",
    "answer": "Stick"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the villain in Jessica Jones who can control minds?",
    "answer": "Kilgrave"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Jessica Jone's bff and adoptive sister?",
    "answer": "Trish Walker"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the barbershop in Luke Cage?",
    "answer": "Pop's barbershop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who runs the nightclub in Luke Cage?",
    "answer": "Cottonmouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the nurse for the defenders?",
    "answer": "Claire Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Luke Cage's half-brother?",
    "answer": "Willis Stryker (Diamondback)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the city Danny Rand trains in?",
    "answer": "K'un-Lun"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Danny Rand's company?",
    "answer": "Rand Enterprises"
  },
  {
    "question": "What martial arts dojo is run by Colleen Wing?",
    "answer": "Chikara Dojo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the main antagonist of the defenders?",
    "answer": "Alexandra Reid"
  },
  {
    "question": "What iconic New York building collapses in the finale of the Defenders?",
    "answer": "Midland Circle Building"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Luke Cage's real name?",
    "answer": "Carl Lucas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hawkeye has a sleeve tattoo of who in Endgame?",
    "answer": "Dead Samuri Ronin"
  },
  {
    "question": "testset",
    "answer": "testsetsecjio"
  },
  {
    "question": "test",
    "answer": "test2"
  }
]